<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Euroventures on Satyam Kapoor | Site Reliability Engineer based in Frankfurt, Germany</title><link>https://satyamkapoor.com/euroventures/</link><description>Recent content in Euroventures on Satyam Kapoor | Site Reliability Engineer based in Frankfurt, Germany</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>satyam@satyamkapoor.com (Satyam Kapoor)</managingEditor><webMaster>satyam@satyamkapoor.com (Satyam Kapoor)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:43:28 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://satyamkapoor.com/euroventures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Culinary Delights in Brussels 🇧🇪</title><link>https://satyamkapoor.com/euroventures/culinary-delights-in-belgium/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:00:01 +0200</pubDate><author>satyam@satyamkapoor.com (Satyam Kapoor)</author><guid>https://satyamkapoor.com/euroventures/culinary-delights-in-belgium/</guid><description>Best food places in Brussels curated by Satyam Kapoor</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="exploring-culinary-delights-in-belgium">Exploring Culinary Delights in Belgium</h2>
<p>Start your culinary journey with the perfect soundtrack and immerse yourself in the flavors and rhythms of Belgium along with exploring the city&rsquo;s best bites.</p>

   <center> <iframe src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/track/4sOjKbpa7RLZVRNxcO26eb?utm_source=generator&amp;theme=0" width="300" height="80" frameborder="0" allowtransparency="true" allow="encrypted-media"></iframe></center>



<h3 id="breakfast-in-brussels">Breakfast in Brussels</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<p><a href="https://leopoldcafepresse.com/">Leopold Café Presse, Etterbeek</a>: Discover a cozy morning sanctuary perfect for lazy brunches or spontaneous meetups. At Leopold Café Presse, savor their invigorating mint tea and indulge in their signature toast omelette amidst a vibrant atmosphere and eclectic beer selection.</p>
<p><code>Tried and loved: Mint tea with toast &amp; omelette 🍵🍳</code></p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/PKvmjpHPuUJKfsSy7">Paul, Etterbeek</a>: Immerse yourself in authentic French bakery delights at Paul. Known for its impeccable quality and freshly baked goods, Paul offers a delightful array of pastries, bread, and coffee. Don&rsquo;t miss their perfectly flaky croissants prepared fresh every morning.</p>
<p><code>☕ Great coffee and fresh croissants 🥐</code></p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/krRbFQxKYHdP57zv7">Brunch Corner, Schaerbeek</a>: Embark on a culinary journey at Brunch Corner in Schaerbeek, a hidden gem offering a delightful Turkish breakfast/brunch experience with a wide array of vegetarian options. From savory böreks to fluffy borek, indulge in the vibrant flavors of Turkish cuisine in a warm and inviting atmosphere.
<code>Cuisine: Turkish</code></p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="http://www.lafabriqueresto.be/">La Fabrique, Brussels</a>: Nestled in a scenic park in Brussels&rsquo; city center, La Fabrique offers a charming ambiance but may suffer from disorganized seating despite reservations. Despite this, it delights with a diverse menu featuring vegetarian and vegan options. However, portion sizes may leave diners wanting more. Despite minor setbacks, La Fabrique remains a promising culinary spot, providing a tranquil escape amidst the city&rsquo;s hustle.
<code>Located in a small park 🌿</code></p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="brunch-and-dinner">Brunch and Dinner</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<p><a href="https://www.manhattns.com/">Manhattn Burgers</a>: Indulge in amazing burgers with fries and homemade lemonade at Manhattn Burgers. Don&rsquo;t miss out on trying their secret sauce with fries for a flavor-packed experience. Vegetarians will also find delight in their Brooklyn Falafel Burger.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="https://lapiolapizza.com/">La Piola Pizza</a>: Experience authentic Italian flavors at La Piola Pizza, where each bite transports you to the streets of Naples. From classic margheritas to gourmet creations, their pizzas are a must-try for any pizza enthusiast.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="https://www.demasalabox.com/">De Masala Box</a>: Savor the fusion of Indian and international flavors at De Masala Box, where traditional Indian wraps meet modern culinary innovation. Don&rsquo;t miss their tantalizing Indian fusion wraps bursting with spices and flavors.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="https://www.nonalife.com/">Nona Pizza</a>: Treat yourself to the taste of Italy at Nona Pizza, where artisanal pizzas are crafted with the finest ingredients and baked to perfection in a wood-fired oven. From classic favorites to creative combinations, there&rsquo;s a pizza for every palate at Nona Pizza.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="https://www.albacioixelles.com/">Al Baccio Pizzeria</a>: Dive into a slice of Italy at Al Baccio Pizzeria, where authentic Neapolitan pizzas are served with a smile. With a focus on quality ingredients and traditional recipes, each bite is a taste of Italy&rsquo;s culinary heritage.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="https://saravanaabhavan.eu/brussels/">Saravana Bhawan</a>: Embark on a gastronomic journey to South India at Saravana Bhawan, renowned for its authentic vegetarian cuisine and traditional flavors. From dosas to idlis, every dish is a celebration of South Indian culinary excellence.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="https://www.facebook.com/kingofshawarma.be/">King of Shawarma Saint Josse Ten Noode</a>: Indulge in the rich flavors of Syrian cuisine at King of Shawarma Saint Josse Ten Noode, where succulent shawarmas and flavorful falafels are served with warm hospitality. Each bite is a taste of Middle Eastern tradition and hospitality.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><a href="https://youwok.be/nl/">You Wok</a>: Dive into a world of noodles and rice at You Wok, where fresh ingredients and bold flavors come together to create mouthwatering Asian-inspired dishes. Whether you crave spicy noodles or fragrant rice, You Wok has something to satisfy every craving.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="247-emergency-food">24/7 Emergency Food</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/mYzB65AXYvPnUYHq8">Esso Gas Station</a>: Need a quick bite on the go? Head to Esso Gas Station for 24/7 convenience and a variety of food options to fuel your journey. From sandwiches to pizza and pasta, you&rsquo;ll find everything you need to satisfy your hunger, anytime, anywhere.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="best-snack-place">Best Snack Place</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://duckduckgo.com/?q=snack&#43;tomberg&amp;t=newext&amp;atb=v361-1&amp;ia=web&amp;iaxm=places">Snack Tomberg</a>: For the best snacks in town, look no further than Snack Tomberg. Whether you&rsquo;re craving crispy fries, savory sandwiches, or indulgent burgers, Snack Tomberg has something to satisfy.</li>
</ul>
]]></content></item></channel></rss>